We are in Khao Lak, Thailand!
Today we are going on an excursion to a waterfall!
- It will be really cool!
- Yes, and of course you should come along.
But first we should go and braid Harry's hair.
Yes, to check out Alma!
- Nice, huh?
- There are even pearls in the hair.
When Harry saw how nice it was, he said he wanted the same.
We will fix that first and then it will be an excursion!
Mom is a little busy working so she stays at the hotel.
Is everything good with the beads?
Only one.
I'll fix it for you.
Maybe you even see it?
- Oh, God!
There you do not want to fall down!
- Oh oh oh!
Whoa, take it easy!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Okay, there was a proper drop.
On this page we have incredibly dense vegetation.
- Do you know what that means, Alma?
- Jungle!
Yes, but ... "vegetation";
So it is very dense vegetation.
- Jungle!
- Yes, it's a jungle.
Check out how beautiful it is!
Is it okay to go in sandals, Alma?
Yes...
As well as...
It's spa fish!
Down here...
Check out, they come right away!
Ouch!
- How does it feel?
- They ...
So they take chews!
They take chews of my heels!
After all, I have those parmesan heels.
- May I look at the heels?
- They just "Oh, Parmesan!".
Here are my heels.
Uäää ...
"Uääää"!